Register of the Henry Regnery Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Correspondence File, 1947-1978 (Box 1-81)
  - Nathan, Beatrice Stephens, 1956-1957 (Folder 55: 17)
  - National Association of College Stores, 1964-1967 (Folder 55: 18)
  - National Association of Manufacturers, 1961-1967 (Folder 55: 19)
  - National Bookbinding Company, 1968 (Folder 55: 20)
  - National Captive Nations Committee, 1960-1964 (Folder 55: 21)
  - National Catholic Conference for International Justice, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 56: 1)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1964-1967 (Folder 56: 2)
  - National Council for Prevention of War, 1945-1955 (Folder 56: 3)
  - National Economic Council, 1964 (Folder 56: 4)
  - National Federation of Conservative Organizations, 1965 (Folder 56: 5)
  - National Forensic League, 1962-1965 (Folder 56: 6)
  - National Republican Congressional Committee, 1965-1966 (Folder 56: 7)
  - National Review, 1957-1979 (Folder 56: 8)
  - National Right to Work Committee, 1960-1967 (Folder 56: 9)
  - Navajivan Trust, 1949-1950 (Folder 56: 10)
  - Navrozov, Lev, 1978-1979 (Folder 56: 11)
  - Nef, John U., 1946-1966 (Box-folder 57: 1)
  - Neill, John R., 1965-1967 (Folder 57: 2)
  - Nelson, Frederic, 1956-1963 (Folder 57: 3)
  - Nettl, Paul, 1955-1956 (Folder 57: 4)
  - Neuerburg, Walter, 1963-1971 (Folder 57: 5)
  - Neuman, Ruth Vendley, 1962-1966 (Folder 57: 6)
  - Newburg, Olga, 1951-1957 (Folder 57: 7)
  - New Paltz State University, 1968 (Folder 57: 8)
  - Newton, Courtland, Jr., 1966-1967 (Folder 57: 9)
  - Nicolaus, R. H., 1977 (Folder 57: 10)
  - Nielsen, Mrs. A. E., 1965 (Folder 57: 11)
  - Nielsen (A. C.) Company, 1965-1967 (Folder 57: 12)
  - Niemeyer, Gerhart, 1964-1975 (Folder 57: 13)
  - Nietzsche, Friedrich, 1963 (Folder 57: 14)
  - Nigg, Walter, 1949-1954 (Folder 57: 15)
  - Nixon, Richard, 1970 (Folder 57: 16)
  - Nock, Francis Jay, 1948-1964 (Folder 57: 17)
  - Nock, Samuel A., 1947-1965 (Folder 57: 18)
  - Nonnenmacher, Nicholas T., 1953-1956 (Folder 57: 19)
  - Norris, Louis W., 1956-1976 (Box-folder 58: 1)
  - Norris, Murray, 1977 (Folder 58: 2)
  - Northwestern University, 1965-1969 (Folder 58: 3)
  - Northwestern Young Conservative Club, 1963 (Folder 58: 4)
  - Notaro, Michael R., 1970-1971 (Folder 58: 5)
  - Nutter, G. Warren, 1962-1975 (Folder 58: 6)
  - Nyaradi, Nicholas, 1965 (Folder 58: 7)
  - Nymeyer, Frederick, 1953-1966 (Folder 58: 8)
  - O (general) (Folder 58: 9)
  - O'Connor, Edward M., 1957-1968 (Folder 58: 10)
  - Oesterreicher, John M., 1949-1950 (Folder 58: 11)
  - Ogilvie, Richard B., 1963-1969 (Folder 58: 12)
  - Ohlendorf, Adelaide, 1963 (Folder 58: 13)
  - Olsberg, Gloria Gras, 1977 (Folder 58: 14)
  - Open Court Publishing Company, 1964-1972 (Folder 58: 15)
  - Opitz, Edmund A., 1957-1977 (Folder 58: 16)
  - Oppen, Beate Ruhm von, 1964-1967 (Folder 58: 17)
  - Orlow, D. Lincoln, 1952-1955 (Folder 58: 18)
  - O'Roark, James F., 1977 (Folder 58: 19)
  - Orton, William A., 1952 (Folder 58: 20)
  - Otto von Hapsburg, Archduke, 1955-1964 (Box-folder 59: 1)
  - Overholser, James A., 1965 (Folder 59: 2)
  - Oz, 1963-1966 (Folder 59: 3)
  - P (general) (Folder 59: 4)
  - Paco d'Arcos, Joaquim, 1967-1975 (Folder 59: 5)
  - Palazzeschi, Aldo, 1953 (Folder 59: 6)
  - Palyi, Melchior, 1947-1971 (Folder 59: 7)
  - Panichas, George A., 1971-1978 (Folder 59: 8)
  - Panther Publications, 1964-1966 (Folder 59: 9)
  - Panuch, J. Anthony, 1954 (Folder 59: 10)
  - Paolucci, Henry, 1960-1978 (Folder 60: 1)
  - Paperbound Books in Print, 1965 (Folder 60: 2)
  - Parents' Magazine, 1966-1968 (Folder 60: 3)
  - Parmentel, Noel E., Jr., 1965-1967 (Folder 60: 4)
  - Paszkiewicz, Henry, 1964 (Folder 60: 5)
  - Paton, William A., 1960-1966 (Folder 60: 6)
  - Patterson, James, 1954 (Folder 60: 7)
  - Patterson, Robert T., 1963-1967 (Folder 60: 8)
  - Patton, Beatrice, 1945-1952 (Folder 60: 9)
  - Peek, David A., 1977-1978 (Folder 60: 10)
  - Peeters, Paul, 1960-1967 (Folder 60: 11)
  - Pegis, Anton C., 1952 (Folder 60: 12)
  - Pel, Mario, 1962-1963 (Folder 60: 13)
  - Pell, Robert T. de Painelle, 1960-1964 (Folder 60: 14)
  - Pencak, William, 1978 (Folder 60: 15)
  - Penniman, Howard, 1957-1966 (Folder 60: 16)
  - Petersen, Clarence, 1968 (Folder 60: 17)
  - Peterson, William H., 1960-1975 (Folder 60: 18)
  - Petro, Sylvester, 1960-1962 (Folder 60: 19)
  - Pettee, George S., 1947 (Folder 60: 20)
  - Pew, J. Howard, 1953-1969 (Folder 60: 21)
  - Pfafflin, Friedrich, 1970 (Folder 60: 22)
  - Pfeiffer, Verlag J., 1967 (Box-folder 61: 1)
  - Phalen, Alice D., 1978 (Folder 61: 2)
  - Philadelphia Society, 1964-1978 (Folder 61: 3)
  - Philipson, Morris, 1978 (Folder 61: 4)
  - Phillips, Norman R., 1977 (Folder 61: 5)
  - Phillips, R. Hart, 1969-1978 (Folder 61: 6)
  - Picard, Max, 1953 (Folder 61: 7)
  - Pichler, Hans, 1965 (Folder 61: 8)
  - Pick, John F., 1956 (Folder 61: 9)
  - Pieper, Josef, 1950-1974 (Folder 61: 10)
  - Pilet, J. A., 1960-1965 (Folder 61: 11)
  - Pilot, 1965 (Folder 61: 12)
  - Piper (R.) and Company Verlag, 1957-1971 (Folder 61: 13)
  - Playboy, 1963 (Folder 61: 14)
  - Pliss, Louise, 1961-1962 (Folder 61: 15)
  - Plotnick, Harvey, 1968-1969 (Folder 61: 16)
  - Polin, Raymond, 1964-1965 (Folder 61: 17)
  - Polner, Murray, 1965-1965 (Folder 61: 18)
  - Portmann, Adolf, 1952 (Folder 61: 19)
  - Possony, Stefan T., 1967-1968 (Folder 61: 20)
  - Powell, James M. S., 1967-1968 (Box-folder 62: 1)
  - Prell, Edward H., 1967 (Folder 62: 2)
  - Prentiss, Spencer, 1978 (Folder 62: 3)
  - Presse- und Informationsamt der Bundesregierung, 1962-1966 (Folder 62: 4)
  - Prezzolini, Giuseppe, 1962 (Folder 62: 5)
  - Prosser, David, Jr., 1964-1965 (Folder 62: 6)
  - Proxmire, William, 1965-1966 (Folder 62: 7)
  - Public Affairs Service Associates, 1965-1966 (Folder 62: 8)
  - Publishers' Weekly, 1951 (Folder 62: 9)
  - Putnam and Company, 1961-1965 (Folder 62: 10)
  - Pyziur, Eugene, 1969 (Folder 62: 11)
  - Quilici, George L., 1967-1968 (Folder 62: 12)
  - R (general) (Folder 62: 13)
  - Radnitzky, Gerard, 1977 (Folder 62: 14)
  - Radvanyi, Janos, 1977 (Folder 62: 15)
  - Rand McNally and Company, 1964-1969 (Folder 62: 16)
  - Randall, Clarence B., 1964 (Folder 62: 17)
  - Random House, 1964-1967 (Folder 62: 18)
  - Ravines, Eudocio, 1960 (Folder 62: 19)
  - Ray, Philip Alexander, 1962-1966 (Folder 62: 20)
  - Raymond, Edward A., 1978 (Folder 62: 21)
  - Read, James M., 1963-1969 (Folder 62: 22)
  - Reader's Digest, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 63: 1)
  - Ready, William, 1968-1973 (Folder 63: 2)
  - Reagan, Ronald, 1970-1971 (Folder 63: 3)
  - Reed, Philip, 1953-1977 (Folder 63: 4)
  - Regan, Ben, 1966 (Folder 63: 5)
  - Reich, John, 1964-1970 (Folder 63: 6)
  - Reilly, Frank E., 1966-1975 (Folder 63: 7)
  - Reilly, John R., 1960-1966 (Folder 63: 8)
  - Reilly and Lee Company, 1960-1968 (Folder 63: 9)
  - Reinhardt, Guenther, 1952-1953 (Folder 63: 10)
  - Reinhardt (Ernst) Verlag, 1964-1966 (Folder 63: 11)
  - Religion and Society, 1968-1969 (Folder 63: 12)
  - Relm Foundation, 1956-1969 (Folder 63: 13)
  - Renterghem, Lemont A., 1967 (Folder 63: 14)
  - Rentsch (Eugen) Verlag, 1956-1972 (Folder 63: 15)
  - Rentschler, William H., 1965-1969 (Box-folder 64: 1)
  - Reporter, 1963-1967 (Folder 64: 2)
  - Republican Educational Foundation, 1955 (Folder 64: 3)
  - Republican National Committee, 1965-1967 (Folder 64: 4)
  - Reswick, William, 1952-1953 (Folder 64: 5)
  - Rewald, John, 1956 (Folder 64: 6)
  - Rhein-Verlag, 1962-1966 (Folder 64: 7)
  - Rheinstein, Max, 1957-1974 (Folder 64: 8)
  - Rhodes, James M., 1977 (Folder 64: 9)
  - Richards, Walter A., 1963 (Folder 64: 10)
  - Richardson, John P., 1978 (Folder 64: 11)
  - Richardson, Robert R., 1962-1967 (Folder 64: 12)
  - Richardson Foundation, 1957 (Folder 64: 13)
  - Richberg, Donald R., 1955-1956 (Folder 64: 14)
  - Richmond News Leader, 1955-1957 (Folder 64: 15)
  - Richter, Werner, 1955-1957 (Folder 64: 16)
  - Rickenbacker, Edward V., 1962-1965 (Folder 64: 17)
  - Rickenbacker, William F., 1974-1979 (Folder 64: 18)
  - Ridgway, M. B., 1954 (Folder 64: 19)
  - Riezler, Kurt, 1949-1952 (Folder 64: 20)
  - Rigney, Harold W., 1956-1967 (Folder 64: 21)
  - Rilke, Rainer Maria, 1950 (Folder 64: 22)
  - Rinkel, L. I., 1977 (Folder 64: 23)
  - Rinn, Verlag Hermann, 1956 (Folder 64: 24)
  - Rinser, Luise, 1956-1957 (Folder 64: 25)
  - Rippy, J. Fred, 1964-1966 (Folder 64: 26)
  - Ritchie, Robert, 1977 (Box-folder 65: 1)
  - Roberts, Joe M., 1966 (Folder 65: 2)
  - Roberts, William P., 1978 (Folder 65: 3)
  - Roche, Paul, 1956 (Folder 65: 4)
  - Rockefeller, David, 1947-1964 (Folder 65: 5)
  - Roepke, Wilhelm, 1949-1970 (Folder 65: 6)
  - Rogers, Donald I., 1970 (Folder 65: 7)
  - Rogers, Michael D., 1978 (Folder 65: 8)
  - Rogge, Benjamin A., 1965-1972 (Folder 65: 9)
  - Rombach, Verlag, 1967 (Folder 65: 10)
  - Roosevelt, Archibald B., 1953 (Folder 65: 11)
  - Roosevelt University, 1968-1975 (Folder 65: 12)
  - Root, E. Merrill, 1953 (Folder 65: 13)
  - Roth, Carl F., 1977 (Folder 65: 14)
  - Roth, William R., 1957 (Folder 65: 15)
  - Rothfels, Hans, 1947-1968 (Folder 65: 16)
  - Routledge and Kegan Paul Company, 1957-1967 (Folder 65: 17)
  - Rowe, David N., 1968 (Folder 65: 18)
  - Royko, Mike, 1967 (Folder 65: 19)
  - Royo, Rodrigo, 1953-1973 (Folder 65: 20)
  - Royster, Vermont C., 1964-1975 (Folder 65: 21)
  - Rozek, Edward J., 1963-1977 (Folder 65: 22)
  - Rubien, Ira, 1964-1965 (Folder 65: 23)
  - Rubin, Morris H., 1949-1975 (Folder 65: 24)
  - Rudge (Fred) Associates, Inc., 1961-1967 (Box-folder 66: 1)
  - Rudin, Harry R., 1949-1957 (Folder 66: 2)
  - Ruedell, Alexander E., 1955-1973 (Folder 66: 3)
  - Rueff, Jacques, 1965-1972 (Folder 66: 4)
  - Ruetten und Loening Verlag, 1966 (Folder 66: 5)
  - Ruff, Lajos, 1965 (Folder 66: 6)
  - Rumely, Edward A., 1957-1973 (Folder 66: 7)
  - Russegger, Friedrich E., 1966-1970 (Folder 66: 8)
  - Russell, Donald, 1960-1970 (Folder 66: 9)
  - Ryder, David Warren, 1954 (Folder 66: 10)
  - Rynne, Xavier, 1967 (Folder 66: 11)
  - Ryskind, Morrie, 1954 (Folder 66: 12)
  - S (general) (Folder 66: 13)
  - Sagehorn, Robert E., 1967 (Box-folder 67: 1)
  - Salnikov, I. S., 1956 (Folder 67: 2)
  - Salter, Robert W., 1965-1966 (Folder 67: 3)
  - Salvatori, Henry, 1977-1978 (Folder 67: 4)
  - Sampson, Emma Speed, 1961 (Folder 67: 5)
  - Sams, Howard W., 1966 (Folder 67: 6)
  - Samsonite Corporation, 1965 (Folder 67: 7)
  - Sandoz, Mari, 1962-1963 (Folder 67: 8)
  - Sattler, Dieter, 1962 (Folder 67: 9)
  - Saturday Review, 1960-1967 (Folder 67: 10)
  - Saxon, O. Glenn, 1961-1962 (Folder 67: 11)
  - Sayles, E. B., 1960-1966 (Folder 67: 12)
  - Scamehorn, Howard L., 1956 (Folder 67: 13)
  - Schacher, Wendy, 1978 (Folder 67: 14)
  - Schapiro, Leonard, 1964 (Folder 67: 15)
  - Scharmel, Iris, 1964 (Folder 67: 16)
  - Scheffer, Paul, 1948-1951 (Folder 67: 17)
  - Scheffler, Verlag Heinrich, 1966 (Folder 67: 18)
  - Scheibla, Shirley, 1968 (Folder 67: 19)
  - Schlafly, Phyllis, 1957-1957 (Folder 67: 20)
  - Schlamm, William S., 1953-1977 (Folder 67: 21)
  - Schlichtenmayer, Verlag Fritz, 1964 (Folder 67: 22)
  - Schmidt, Donald H., 1977 (Box-folder 68: 1)
  - Schmidt, Godfrey P., 1962 (Folder 68: 2)
  - Schneekluth (Franz) Verlag, 1955-1956 (Folder 68: 3)
  - Schneider, Franz, 1960-1978 (Folder 68: 4)
  - Schneider, Georg Wenzel, 1964 (Folder 68: 5)
  - Schoeman, Byron, 1963-1971 (Folder 68: 6)
  - Schoenberger, Guido, 1951 (Folder 68: 7)
  - Scholz, Janos, 1952-1974 (Folder 68: 8)
  - Schreiber, G. R., 1965 (Folder 68: 9)
  - Schroder, Raymond V., 1958 (Folder 68: 10)
  - Schroeder (Marion von) Verlag, 1957 (Folder 68: 11)
  - Schultz, Helen E., 1978 (Folder 68: 12)
  - Schuyler, Ruby, 1962 (Folder 68: 13)
  - Schwabe (Benno) and Company Verlag, 1956-1962 (Folder 68: 14)
  - Schwarz, Rudolf, 1959-1966 (Folder 68: 15)
  - Scribner's Sons, Charles, 1962-1978 (Folder 68: 16)
  - Seagle, William, 1957 (Folder 68: 17)
  - Sedlmayr, Hans, 1963 (Folder 68: 18)
  - Seewald Verlag, 1965-1970 (Folder 68: 19)
  - Seifert, Helmut, 1966-1976 (Folder 68: 20)
  - Sensei, Mauro, 1953-1970 (Folder 68: 21)
  - Seroff, Victor, 1977-1978 (Folder 68: 22)
  - Sevella, Ephraim, 1978 (Folder 68: 23)
  - Shafer, Joseph E., 1964 (Folder 68: 24)
  - Shannon, Ian, 1965-1966 (Folder 68: 25)
  - Shapiro, Edward S., 1978 (Folder 68: 26)
  - Sheed and Ward Company, 1956-1970 (Folder 68: 27)
  - Sheehan, Timothy P., 1957 (Folder 68: 28)
  - Shenoy, B. R., 1963 (Folder 68: 29)
  - Shepperd, John Ben, 1957 (Folder 68: 30)
  - Shiappa, Gerard F., 1977 (Folder 68: 31)
  - Shinner Foundations, 1956-1957 (Folder 68: 32)
  - Shoham, Shlomo, 1964 (Box-folder 69: 1)
  - Shorey, Kenneth Paul, 1964-1965 (Folder 69: 2)
  - Shumway, Mary, 1964 (Folder 69: 3)
  - Shwayder Brothers Company, 1964-1965 (Folder 69: 4)
  - Sievers, Harry J., 1951-1952 (Folder 69: 5)
  - Simmonds, Christopher, 1966 (Folder 69: 6)
  - Simson, Otto G. von, 1948-1949 (Folder 69: 7)
  - Sinclair, Bondeson and Company, 1949 (Folder 69: 8)
  - Singh, P. N., 1964 (Folder 69: 9)
  - Slater, H. N., 1964-1966 (Folder 69: 10)
  - Sleeper, Raymond, 1969 (Folder 69: 11)
  - Slusser, Herbert, 1956 (Folder 69: 12)
  - Small, Joseph, 1949 (Folder 69: 13)
  - Smeeth, William Beye, 1968 (Folder 69: 14)
  - Smith, Alson J., 1953-1956 (Folder 69: 15)
  - Smith, Hermon D., 1969 (Folder 69: 16)
  - Smith, Hilda W., 1978 (Folder 69: 17)
  - Smith, John Wesley Brabner, 1949 (Folder 69: 18)
  - Smith, Mortimer, 1949-1973 (Folder 69: 19)
  - Smith, Ronald, 1968 (Folder 69: 20)
  - Smith, Truman, 1949-1969 (Folder 69: 21)
  - Smith, William Jay, 1955-1978 (Folder 69: 22)
  - Smoot, Dan, 1952-1962 (Box-folder 70: 1)
  - Snell, Dewitt S., 1978 (Folder 70: 2)
  - Snyder (Henry M.) and Company, 1966 (Folder 70: 3)
  - Sobell, M. Henry, Jr., (Mrs.), 1966-1968 (Folder 70: 4)
  - Society of Midland Authors, 1964-1965 (Folder 70: 5)
  - Sohl, Frederic J., 1966 (Folder 70: 6)
  - Sokolsky, George E., 1951-1953 (Folder 70: 7)
  - Solzhenitsyn, Alexander, 1979 (Folder 70: 8)
  - Sorokin, Pitirim A., 1956-1977 (Folder 70: 9)
  - Soseki, Natsume, 1957 (Folder 70: 10)
  - Sousa Pernes, Barbara de, 1963 (Folder 70: 11)
  - South Africa, Information Service of, 1964 (Folder 70: 12)
  - South Puerto Rico Sugar Company, 1963-1965 (Folder 70: 13)
  - Southern States Industrial Council, 1957-1966 (Folder 70: 14)
  - Spacek, Leonard P., 1961-1968 (Folder 70: 15)
  - Spadaro, Louis M., 1977 (Folder 70: 16)
  - Spanish Embassy, Washington, D.C., 1956-1960 (Folder 70: 17)
  - Speidel, Hans, 1949-1955 (Folder 70: 18)
  - Spiethoff, Arthur, 1955 (Folder 70: 19)
  - Stadtmueller, Georg, 1965 (Folder 70: 20)
  - Standley, William H., 1955-1957 (Folder 70: 21)
  - Stanford University, 1968 (Folder 70: 22)
  - Stassen, John H., 1965-1966 (Folder 70: 23)
  - Stavrianos, L. S., 1951 (Folder 70: 24)
  - Stecchini, Livio C., 1952-1953 (Folder 70: 25)
  - Steel Corporation, United States, 1960-1965 (Folder 70: 26)
  - Steele, Peter, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 71: 1)
  - Stehr, Wolfgang, 1963 (Folder 71: 2)
  - Stein, Edith, n.d. (Folder 71: 3)
  - Steincrohn, Peter J., 1968-1969 (Folder 71: 4)
  - Stevens, Mary Ellen, 1961 (Folder 71: 5)
  - Stevenson, Adlai, 1979 (Folder 71: 6)
  - Stevenson, Carol, 1961 (Folder 71: 7)
  - Steward, Ann, 1963-1964 (Folder 71: 8)
  - Stigler, George, 1965-1970 (Folder 71: 9)
  - Stock, Noel, 1960-1972 (Folder 71: 10)
  - Stocker (Leopold) Verlag, 1965 (Folder 71: 11)
  - Stokes, Dillard, 1956-1957 (Folder 71: 12)
  - Stone, Geoffrey, 1951-1952 (Folder 71: 13)
  - Stone, W. Clement, 1960-1972 (Folder 71: 14)
  - Strauss, Franz Joseph, 1973 (Folder 71: 15)
  - Strauss, Leo, 1966-1968 (Folder 71: 16)
  - Strausz-Hupe, Robert, 1968 (Folder 71: 17)
  - Stuart, H. L., 1953-1966 (Folder 71: 18)
  - Sudler, Louis, 1969-1976 (Folder 71: 19)
  - Sullivan, Kay, 1968 (Folder 71: 20)
  - Surette, Leon, 1978 (Folder 71: 21)
  - Syracuse University, 1966-1969 (Folder 71: 22)
  - Syrian Embassy, Washington, D.C., 1964 (Folder 71: 23)
  - Szaz, Zoltan Michael, 1957-1969 (Folder 71: 24)
  - T (general) (Box-folder 72: 1)
  - Taeuber, Irene, 1947 (Folder 72: 2)
  - Tansill, Charles Callin, 1955-1976 (Folder 72: 3)
  - Tappe, Horst, 1966 (Folder 72: 4)
  - Tate, Allen, 1953-1955 (Folder 72: 5)
  - Taylor, Walter F., 1949-1967 (Folder 72: 6)
  - Telford, Kenneth A., 1960-1968 (Folder 72: 7)
  - Teller, Edward, 1973 (Folder 72: 8)
  - Tensen De Witte, Ruth, 1968-1978 (Folder 72: 9)
  - Terrill, Dean, 1960-1970 (Folder 72: 10)
  - Thames and Hudson Company, 1964-1971 (Folder 72: 11)
  - Thibon, Gustave, 1952-1953 (Folder 72: 12)
  - Thompson, Edgar K., 1965 (Folder 72: 13)
  - Thompson, Ruth Plumly, 1963-1967 (Folder 72: 14)
  - Thompson, Samuel M., 1957-1973 (Folder 72: 15)
  - Thorin, Duane W., 1956-1970 (Folder 72: 16)
  - Thornton, Robert M., 1955-1965 (Folder 72: 17)
  - Three R Schools, 1960-1967 (Folder 72: 18)
  - Thurmond, Strom, 1972 (Folder 72: 19)
  - Tillich, Paul, 1964 (Box-folder 73: 1)
  - Time, 1967-1968 (Folder 73: 2)
  - Toal, M. F., 1963-1975 (Folder 73: 3)
  - Todrank, Gustave H., 1977 (Folder 73: 4)
  - Tonsor, Stephen J., 1967-1979 (Folder 73: 5A-5B)
  - Trace, Arthur S., Jr., 1964-1965 (Folder 73: 6)
  - Trigg, Adelaide, 1977 (Folder 73: 7)
  - Tripp, Chester Dudley, 1965 (Folder 73: 8)
  - Trohan, Walter, 1970-1978 (Folder 73: 9)
  - Tso, Frederick L., 1952 (Folder 73: 10)
  - Turen, Teppo, 1963-1965 (Folder 73: 11)
  - Tyrrell, R. Emmett, Jr., 1972-1979 (Folder 73: 12)
  - Tyrmand, Leopold, 1977-1979 (Folder 73: 13)
  - Tyson, Jeffery Lord, 1965 (Folder 73: 14)
  - U (general) (Folder 73: 15)
  - Ulam, Adam, 1974-1978 (Folder 73: 16)
  - Unamuno, Fernando de, 1967 (Folder 73: 17)
  - Unidentified, 1953-1977 (Folder 73: 18)
  - United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization, 1964-1968 (Folder 73: 19)
  - United States Information Agency, 1957-1973 (Folder 73: 20)
  - University of Chicago, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 74: 1)
  - University of Notre Dame, 1967-1969 (Folder 74: 2)
  - Upton, John, 1956 (Folder 74: 3)
  - Upton, Miller, 1965-1971 (Folder 74: 4)
  - Utley, Freda, 1948-1976 (Folder 74: 5)
  - Utley, Jon Basil, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 75: 1)
  - V (general) (Folder 75: 2)
  - Valdeiglesias, Marques de, 1956-1957 (Folder 75: 3)
  - Valenti, Fernando, 1978 (Folder 75: 4)
  - Valentine, Alan, 1956 (Folder 75: 5)
  - Vallee, Jacques F., 1964-1966 (Folder 75: 6)
  - Van Altena, John P., Jr., 1967-1968 (Folder 75: 7)
  - Van den Haag, Ernest, 1970-1973 (Folder 75: 8)
  - Vann, Gerald, n.d. (Folder 75: 9)
  - Varnell, O. Paul, 1966 (Folder 75: 10)
  - Veatch, Henry B., 1965-1966 (Folder 75: 11)
  - Veeck, William, 1967 (Folder 75: 12)
  - Vicker, Ray, 1961-1970 (Folder 75: 13)
  - Victor, Joan Berg, 1966 (Folder 75: 14)
  - Viereck, George Sylvester, 1956 (Folder 75: 15)
  - Viereck, Peter, 1950-1964 (Folder 75: 16)
  - Vietta, Egon, 1951 (Folder 75: 17)
  - Viguerie, Richard A., 1966-1978 (Folder 75: 18)
  - Viking Press, 1966 (Folder 75: 19)
  - Villard, Oswald Garrison, 1947 (Folder 75: 20)
  - Vivas, Eliseo, 1963-1975 (Folder 75: 21)
  - Voegelin, Eric, 1956-1978 (Box-folder 76: 1)
  - Vogel, Charles, 1968 (Folder 76: 2)
  - Voldeng, Karl E., 1963 (Folder 76: 3)
  - Volker (William) Fund, 1957-1969 (Folder 76: 4)
  - Vorhies, John R., 1968-1969 (Folder 76: 5)
  - Voss, Earl H., 1962-1974 (Folder 76: 6)
  - Vulcan Press, 1955-1957 (Folder 76: 7)
  - W (general) (Folder 76: 8)
  - W (general) (Box-folder 77: 1)
  - WFMT (radio station), n.d. (Folder 77: 2)
  - Wagner, Geoffrey, 1977 (Folder 77: 3)
  - Waldstein, Barbara, Countess, 1957-1960 (Folder 77: 4)
  - Walgreen, Myrtle R., 1963-1968 (Folder 77: 5)
  - Walker, Edwin A., 1962 (Folder 77: 6)
  - Wall Street Journal, 1967-1979 (Folder 77: 7)
  - Wallace, Willard M., 1962-1966 (Folder 77: 8)
  - Wallis, W. Allen, 1962-1978 (Folder 77: 9)
  - Walton, Joplin, Langer and Company, 1967-1969 (Folder 77: 10)
  - Walz, L. Humphrey, 1957-1964 (Folder 77: 11)
  - Ward, Leo R., 1955-1973 (Folder 77: 12)
  - Washington Report, 1967 (Folder 77: 13)
  - Wathen, Richard B., 1970-1978 (Folder 77: 14)
  - Watters, Ralph G., 1970-1978 (Folder 77: 15)
  - Watts, George, 1950 (Folder 77: 16)
  - Weaver, Richard M., 1953-1967 (Folder 77: 17)
  - Weber, Calvin E., 1963 (Folder 77: 18)
  - Wedemeyer, Albert C., 1951-1966 (Folder 77: 19)
  - Weidenfeld and Nicolson Company, 1962-1967 (Folder 77: 20)
  - Weinrott, Lestar A., 1969-1972 (Folder 77: 21)
  - Weizsaecker, Ernst von, Baron, 1951-1955 (Folder 77: 22)
  - Welch, Robert H. W., Jr., 1951-1978 (Folder 78: 1)
  - Werkbund-Verlag, 1956-1967 (Folder 78: 2)
  - Wess, Harold B., 1969 (Folder 78: 3)
  - Western Policy and Eastern Europe, Conference on, 1965 (Folder 78: 4)
  - Western Publishing Company, 1966 (Folder 78: 5)
  - Wettstein, George M., 1956 (Folder 78: 6)
  - Wetzel, Frank, 1961-1967 (Folder 78: 7)
  - Wetzel, John C., 1968 (Folder 78: 8)
  - Weyhe, Erhard, 1966 (Folder 78: 9)
  - Weyl, Nathaniel, 1962-1973 (Folder 78: 10)
  - Whalen, Richard J., 1967-1976 (Folder 78: 11)
  - Wheelwright and Regnery Company, 1969 (Folder 78: 12)
  - Whigham, Peter, 1965-1966 (Folder 78: 13)
  - Whitcomb, Edgar D., 1957-1967 (Folder 78: 14)
  - White, Donald O., 1967-1968 (Folder 78: 15)
  - White, Peter, 1976-1978 (Folder 78: 16)
  - White Bear, Chief, 1963-1967 (Folder 78: 17)
  - Whitney, Janet, 1951 (Folder 78: 18)
  - Wiechert, Ernst, 1945-1947 (Folder 78: 19)
  - Wilbur, William H., 1953-1973 (Box-folder 79: 1)
  - Wild, John, 1952-1964 (Folder 79: 2)
  - Wiley, Charles W., 1966-1967 (Folder 79: 3)
  - Wilhelmsen, Frederick D., 1955 (Folder 79: 4)
  - Williams, C. Dickerman, 1964-1965 (Folder 79: 5)
  - Williams, Herschel V., 1955 (Folder 79: 6)
  - Willis, Benjamin C., 1965-1969 (Folder 79: 7)
  - Willoughby, Charles A., 1955-1964 (Folder 79: 8)
  - Wills, Garry, 1964-1967 (Folder 79: 9)
  - Wilmowsky, Tilo von, Freiherr, 1951 (Folder 79: 10)
  - Wilson, Catherine R., 1949 (Folder 79: 11)
  - Wilson, Francis G., 1961-1966 (Folder 79: 12)
  - Wilson, Penelope Coker, 1964 (Folder 79: 13)
  - Wilson (Carl K.) Company, 1967 (Folder 79: 14)
  - Winston, Richard, 1951-1964 (Folder 79: 15)
  - Wirth, Otto, 1964-1974 (Folder 79: 16)
  - Wiser, James L., 1977 (Folder 79: 17)
  - Witherell, Louise R., 1965-1966 (Folder 79: 18)
  - Witherspoon, Anne, 1968 (Folder 79: 19)
  - Wittmer, Felix, 1956 (Folder 79: 20)
  - Wohl, Louis de, 1960 (Folder 78: 21)
  - Wolfe, Bertram, 1966-1973 (Folder 79: 22)
  - Wolfe, Ella, 1974-1978 (Folder 79: 23)
  - Wolff (Oswald) Company, 1961-1970 (Folder 79: 24)
  - Wood, Robert E., 1947-1965 (Box-folder 80: 1)
  - Woods, Frank H., 1968 (Folder 80: 2)
  - Worden, George J., 1977 (Folder 80: 3)
  - Works, Nelson, 1963-1975 (Folder 80: 4)
  - Wormser, Felix Edgar, 1961 (Folder 80: 5)
  - Wormser, Rene A., 1953-1978 (Folder 80: 6)
  - Wreszin, Michael, 1964 (Folder 80: 7)
  - Wright, David McCord, 1960-1963 (Folder 80: 8)
  - Wright, Douglas B., 1961 (Folder 80: 9)
  - Wuerthner, J. J., Jr., 1960-1978 (Folder 80: 10)
  - XYZ (general) (Folder 80: 11)
  - Yager, Susanna, 1969 (Folder 80: 12)
  - Yale University Press, 1961-1968 (Folder 80: 13)
  - Yarnall (Polly A.) Associates, 1965 (Folder 80: 14)
  - Young Americans for Freedom, 1960-1974 (Folder 80: 15)
  - Young Canadians For Freedom, 1962 (Box-folder 81: 1)
  - Young, Glenn O., 1969 (Folder 81: 2)
  - Youth Speaks, 1966 (Folder 81: 3)
  - Z (general) (Folder 81: 4)
  - Zbinden, Hans, 1949 (Folder 81: 5)
  - Zimmerman, Carle C., 1962 (Folder 81: 6)
  - Zoll, Donald A., 1970-1974 (Folder 81: 7)
  - Zurcher, Suzette Morton, 1967 (Folder 81: 8)
- Speeches and Writings, 1971-1972 (Box 81)
  Writings by Henry Regnery, arranged alphabetically by title.
  - "Albert J. Nock: An Appreciation,", 1971 (Folder 81: 9)
  - "Eliot, Pound and Lewis: A Creative Friendship,", 1972 (Folder 81: 10)
  - "Henry Regnery: A Conservative Publisher in a Liberal World,", 1971 (Folder 81: 11)